(Past Leonard:)According to the roommate agreement,
I'm entitled to allocate 50 percent...
(Past Leonard:)...of the cubic footage
of common areas.
(Past Sheldon:)But you didn't notify me by e-mail,
so this is still a breach.
(Past Leonard:)I did notify you.
(Past Sheldon:)Oh, you did, did you?
(Past Sheldon:)Drat.
(Past Sheldon:)Hoisted by my own spam filter.
-What am I doing in your spam?
-I put you there after you forwarded me...
(Past Sheldon:)...a picture of a cat playing
the piano entitled "This is funny."
(Past Raj:)Oh, yeah. I saw that. That was hilarious.
Heh-heh-heh.
-What's this have to do with the elevator?
-I'm getting to it.
(Past Sheldon:)I assure you, you'll be sorry
you wasted your money on an iPod...
(Past Sheldon:)...when Microsoft comes out with theirs.